So what do you think?
你认为怎么样？
Casa de Joey.
乔伊的窝
-I decorated it myself. -Get out!
我自己布置的 少来了
Wow,Joey,this is....
乔伊，这个是…
-Art. -Art it is.
艺术 就是艺术
Check this out! Is it a coffee table?
瞧，这是一张咖啡桌呢
Is it a panther? There's no need to decide.
还是一只豹？都无所谓
Hey,nice pillow.
好漂亮的枕头
So tell me, is this genuine Muppet skin?
这是真的布偶皮吗？
Hey,excellent water,table thing.
好极，好极了的桌上型水东西
Thanks. I love this. But you know what?
谢了，我很喜欢这个东西 但你知道吗？
It makes me want to pee.
它会让我想尿尿
Yeah,me too. I think that's the challenge.
对呀，我也是 对呀，我想挑战就在那儿
How come Chandler didn't come?
为什么钱德没来？
It's because he had a thing with the...
因为他有一件事…
...with the thing.
…他有事
Right. I got it.
我懂了
So why don't you show us the rest of your casa?
带我们去参观其他的部分吧
The best part! Come on.
最棒的部分，来…
Nice toilet.
好帅的马桶
No,no,no. Behind it.
不…后面那个
-You have a phone in here? -That's right.
你这里装了电话？ 没错
I have a phone.
我这里装了…
In here.
…电话
Joey,promise me something.
乔伊，答应我一件事
Never call me from that phone.
别用那个电话打给我
The One Where Eddie Moves ln
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第17集 艾迪搬入
Okay,here we go.
来了
Sorry,they were all out of apple pie. Someone just got the last piece.
抱歉，苹果派卖完了 最后一片刚被干掉
Oh,my God! You won't believe this!
天啊…你们绝对不会相信的
I have just been discovered.
我刚刚被发现了
Wait a minute. I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.
等一等，我四年前 就宣布你为法国领地了
Anyway.
总而言之
Don't freak out and say how great this is until I'm done.
答应我，你们不会发狂 直到我说完为止，好吗？
I just met this producer of this teeny record company...
我刚刚认识了一个 小唱片公司的制作人…
...who said that I have a very fresh,offbeat sound...
…她说我的声音很清新 很特别…
...and she wants to do a demo of "Smelly Cat."
…她要帮我录制 “臭臭猫”的试听带
Okay,I told you not to do that yet.
我说过不要太兴奋的
And she wants to do a video.
她还说要帮我做MTV呢
I'm not done yet,okay?
我还没说完
God!
天哪
If that goes well, they may even want to make an album.
如果结果不错的话 他们或许还会帮我做一个专辑
I'm done now.
我说完了
If you care about me, get the pie out of the man's hood.
罗斯，如果你关心我的话 就把馅饼从他帽子里拿出来
-Get the what? -There's a pie in the hood. Go!
拿什么？ 帽子里有馅饼…快去
What are you doing?
你干什么？
I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
对不起，我的馅饼… 在…在你帽子里
I have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants...
现在我得去那个砘锏目阕由 拿我的咖啡…
...and I'll be back in the hospital by 7.
…我七点以前会回医院去
Damn it,Ross! Get your butt out of the bathroom!
该死，罗斯，你快给我滚出来
Calm down. I'm blow-drying.
别激动，我在吹头发
Blow-drying what? You have no hair.
吹什么头发呀？你没有头发啦
What's going on?
怎么了？
Your boyfriend has been in there for an hour!
你男朋友 在里面关了一个多小时
It's like I'm living with him again.
真不敢相信 这就像我们又住在一起
He's here when I go to sleep and wake up and when I want to shower.
我睡觉时他在，醒来时他在 想洗澡的时候他也在
I feel like I'm 16 again.
我好像回到十六岁了
Well,you're not 16. You're both adults now.
你不是十六岁 而且你们现在都是大人了
Get out,you doofus!
出来呀，蠢货
Or,you know, he's rubber and you're glue.
你知道啊 他是橡胶，你是胶水
All yours.
该你了
I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.
希望你清了排水孔的头发
Shut up!
住口
Cut it out!
I've never wanted you more.
我从来没有这样想要过你
So what do you say,boys? Should I call him?
怎么样，孩子们 我该打电话给他吗？
You know what they say:
俗语有云：
Ask your slippers a question...
问你拖鞋一个问题…
...you're going crazy.
…你疯了
I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.
乔伊，对不起 我今天没有过去
That's okay.
没关系
You had a thing.
你…你有事嘛
I hear the place looks great.
对，听说你那里很棒
Forget about it. I'm having a ball!
别提了，我开心死了
How's the apartment?
你那儿怎么样了？
It's terrific. I mean,it's a regular space-...
很…很棒啊 一个空间…
...-fest!
…的大聚合
Well,great.
那太棒了
Yeah,I just...
是呀，我只是…
...wanted to call and say hey.
…打个电话跟你聊一聊而已
Well,okay.
好啊
Was that the oven timer?
那是烤箱定时器吗？
That's right,my friend.
没有错，朋友
It's time for...
应该看…
...Baywatch!
…“海滩游侠”
Can you believe they gave Stephanie skin cancer?
你相信 他们让芬妮得皮肤癌吗？
I can't believe they made her lieutenant!
我还是不敢相信 他们升她为副队长
You're saying that because you love Yasmine Bleeth.
你那么说是因为 你最喜欢毕雅敏了
How could anyone not love Yasmine Bleeth?
怎么可能会有人 不爱毕雅敏呢？
Hey,they're running.
她们在跑了
See,this is the brilliance of the show.
瞧，这个节目棒就棒在这里
I say always keep them running.
我说她们应该不停地跑
All the time running!
一直跑
Run!
跑
Run,Yasmine! Run like the wind!
跑啊，雅敏，像风一样的跑
But you wanted to live by yourself.
我以为你想自己一个人住
I did. I thought it'd be great.
没错，我以为会很棒
I figured I'd have time alone with my thoughts.
我以为我会有时间自己思考
But it turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you think.
但我发觉我的思想 没有你们想的那么多
Why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?
乔伊，你跟钱德说 你想搬回去好了
You really think he'd take me?
你认为他会答应吗？
We had a good talk last night...
我们昨晚聊得很开心…
...but when I moved out, I hurt him bad.
…可是我搬走时把他伤透了
He would definitely want you back.
我保证，他绝对想你搬回去的
I'm telling you, there's no way he's moving back.
我告诉你 他绝对不可能搬回来的
But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night.
可是我们从没像昨天晚上 聊得那么开心过
I mean,it was
那就像是…
It was like when we first started living together.
我们刚刚住在一起时一样
I know you don't want to hear this right now...
钱德 我知道你现在听不进去…
... but we've seen him in his new place. And he's happy.
…但我们看过他在新家的样子 他很快乐
He's decorated.
他都装潢好了
Chandler,he has moved on,okay? You have to,too.
听着，钱德 他向前走了，你也要这样
You'll have to accept the fact that you're just friends now.
你必须接受 我们只是朋友这个事实
You're not...
你们不再是…
... roommates anymore.
…室友了
Okay,Phoebe. You ready to try one?
菲比，可以试了吗？
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
What are they feeding you?
他们喂你什么？
Smelly,smelly,smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
非常臭的臭臭猫
Whoa! Oh,my God!
我的天啊
I mean,like,who was that?
是谁在唱？
They're your backup singers. Behind you,hon.
你的伴唱团，在你后面
I thought they were just watching me.
我还以为她们只是在看
Like at an aquarium,you know?
就像像水族馆那样
All right.
好了
From the top.
从头开始
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
What are they feeding you?
他们喂你什么？
Okay,sorry.
对不起
I'm just not getting...
我没感觉到…
...that everyone gets...
…大家都懂…
... how smelly this cat actually is.
…这只猫到底有多臭
Maybe if we could talk about this...
也许我们应该谈一谈…
... because I need to feel that you really care about the cat.
…因为我必须要感觉到 你们真的…很关心那只猫
We can talk.
我们可以谈的
It's just that this costs $100 a minute to be in here.
只是录音间是算时间的 一分钟一百块耶
So the cat stinks, but you love it. Let's go.
好，那只猫很臭 但你们非常爱它，开始
No,there is no way he was a velociraptor.
不，它绝对不可能 是一只迅猛龙的
Look at the cranial ridge,okay?
不，东尼，你看他的头盖脊骨
If Dino was a velociraptor, he'd have eaten the Flintstones.
帝诺要是一只迅猛龙 它早吃了摩登原始人了
Were you taking a nap?
你在睡觉？
I was.
本来是
Tony,can you hold on? That's the other line.
等等，东尼，等一下，好吗？ 我有插拨
Yeah,she's here, but can she call you back?
对，她在 我叫她回电话，好吗？
Okay,thanks.
好，谢了
Call Joanna.
打给乔安娜
Did she leave a number?
她留了号码？
Did you see me write one down?
你看到我写下来了吗？
I don't have her number,butt-munch.
我没有她的电话，呆瓜
She'll call back. Don't be such a baby.
那她会再打来的 你不要耍孩子脾气了
You're the baby.
我才没有，你自己才是
-Get off my back. -Get out of my face.
听着，你别烦我，好不好？ 你不要碍眼，好不好？
Wait,hold on,Tony. Hold on.
慢着，等一下，东尼
Yeah,she's right here. Hold on.
对，不，她在，等一下
Tony,can I call you back?
东尼，我再打给你，好吗？
That's my sister's boyfriend.
那是我妹妹的男朋友
Give me that.
电话给我
Sweetie,before I forget,did l leave my diaphragm at your place?
甜心，听着，趁我还记得 我的避孕器是否留在你那儿？
Hi,Mom.
妈
So how's the palace?
皇宫生活过得怎么样了？
It's funny you should mention that because I was thinking....
真有趣，既然你提起这个 我在想…
What's with the boxes?
这些箱子怎么回事？
Actually,I have some news.
事实上，我有个消息
Is that Joey guy gonna pick up his moose hat or should I toss it?
那个乔伊会回来拿他的 麋鹿帽吗？还是我把它扔了？
Why don't you ask him yourself? This is my new roommate,Eddie.
这个…你何不自己问他呢？ 乔伊，这是我的新室友艾迪
Nice to meet you.
幸会
-Likewise. -How you doing?
彼此 你好吗？
I'll take that.
那我带走了
It's what I came for.
我就是回来拿这个的
This is new. Where'd you two meet?
这倒新鲜 你们是哪儿认识的？
At the supermarket in the ethnic food section.
我们在超市的民族食品区
I helped him pick out a chorizo.
我帮他挑西班牙香肠
We got to talking. He needed a place,and I had a spare room.
我们开始聊，他说要找地方住 而我又刚好有一个空房
Now it's a spare room?
那儿成了空房了？
Well,yeah. In that it's not being used...
是啊，那房间没有人用…
...and I have it to spare.
…而我就把它空出来
Well,I got what I came for.
我拿到我要的了
I'll see you.
改天见了
Hey,Joe.
乔伊
When'd you start using moose in your hair?
你什么时候开始抹慕丝的？
Is this guy great,or what?
他是不是很棒？
Yeah,he is.
是呀，他很棒
I can't believe he has a new roommate. Who is he?
真不敢相信他有新室友了 这砘锸撬啊？
Eddie. He just met him.
好像叫艾迪，他们刚认识
It'll never last. He's just a rebound roommate.
不会长久的，他只是个替代品
Check it out! Check it out!
看这个…
It's "Smelly Cat," the video!
是“臭臭猫”的MTV
Now,I haven't seen it yet, so if you don't like it...
我自己都还没看呢 如果你们不喜欢的话呢…
...so what? None of you ever made a video.
…那又怎么样？ 你们又没有MTV
Get out of here,cat! You stink!
滚出去，猫，你臭死了
Smoking!
美呆了
Look at me!
看看我
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
What are they feeding you?
他们喂你什么？
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
It's not your fault
那不是你的错
Smelly,smelly,smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
臭臭…，非常臭的臭臭猫
It's not your fault
那不是你的错
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫…
-Oh,my God! -I know.
我的天啊 我知道
I sound amazing!
我的声音好美喔
They won't take you to the vet
他们不带你去看兽医
You're obviously not their favorite pet
你显然不是他们的最爱
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
It's not your fault
那不是你的错
I've never heard myself sing before.
我从没听过自己唱的歌
I mean,except in my own head.
除了在我的头里面
This is so cool! Now I can hear what you hear!
这太酷了 我可以听到你们听到的了
Pretty different,huh?
蛮不同的吧？
I am sorry, but I'm incredibly talented!
不要介意，我实在太才华洋溢
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
It's not your fault
那不是你的错
What's going on,man?
乔伊，近来如何？
Eddie.
艾迪
Morning.
早安
I just came by to pick up my mail.
我只是过来拿我的信
-Where's the mail? -Over there on the table.
信在哪儿？ 在那边那张桌上
You don't keep it on this table anymore?
你不再把信放在这张桌上了？
Eddie likes it over there.
不了，艾迪喜欢把信放在那边
All right,here you go,my friend. Eggs a la Eddie.
好了，请用吧，朋友 这是艾迪秘方蛋
That's great.
太棒了
What?
干嘛？
I thought you liked your eggs...
我只是以为你喜欢…
...with the bread with the hole in the middle,a la me!
…面包挖一个洞，中间放蛋呢
I do,but Eddie makes them this way. They're pretty darn good.
我是喜欢呀，但艾迪是这样 煎的，还真的是蛮好吃的
Well,you guys...
好了，两位…
... I'm out of here.
…我要出去了
See you,pals.
再见，兄弟们
See you.
再见
-How are you two getting along? -I couldn't be happier.
你们处得怎么样？ 再快乐也不过了
Great.
很好
I'm happy for you.
我替你高兴
All right,that's it!
好吧，够了
He just comes in here, Mr. Johnny New Eggs...
那个人就这样进来 新蛋先生…
...with his moving the mail and his "See you,pals."
…变了放信的地方，还有 “再见，兄弟们”
And now there's no juice!
现在果汁也没有了
There's no juice for the people who need the juice. I need the juice!
需要果汁跟要果汁的人没得喝 我需要果汁
There's another carton there.
那边还有一盒果汁啊
This isn't about juice anymore, all right,man?
这不再是关于果汁了，好吗？
All right.
好呀
So what's it about?
那么是关于什么呢？
Eggs!
蛋
Whose eggs do you like better, his or mine?
你比较喜欢谁的蛋？ 他的还是我的？
-Well,I like both eggs equally. -Oh,come on!
我两个一样喜欢 少来了
Nobody likes two eggs equally. I wanna know which one you like better.
没人一样喜欢两种不同的蛋 我知道你比较喜欢哪一种
What's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore.
那有什么差别呢？ 你的蛋已经不在这个地方了
You took your eggs and you left!
你已经带着你的蛋走了
Did you expect me to never find new eggs?
你真的期望 我再也找不到一个新的蛋吗？
I wanna watch Entertainment Tonight.
我要看“今夜娱乐”
Tough. We're watching Predators of the Serengeti.
真不幸 我们要看“瑟伦格提掠食者”
Would you guys stop!
不要吵了，好不好？
It's my TV!
这是我的电视
-Quit it! -Bite me!
你…住手 你咬我呀
Monica keeps changing the channel.
摩妮卡她一直在转台呀
That's great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
棒透了 你去跟妈咪打个小报告啊
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
现在我变成妈咪了
Look,I refuse to get sucked into...
好，听着，我拒绝卷入…
...this weird little Geller dimension thing,okay?
…这一类畸型的盖勒家庭纠纷
So I'm gonna go take a nice long hot bubble bath...
我现在要去洗个 香喷喷热腾腾的泡泡浴…
...because you kids are driving me crazy!
…因为妈咪快要被你们逼疯了
What do we do about this?
这件事我们怎么解决？
We could tape Entertainment Tonight.
我们可以 把“今夜娱乐”录下来
Not that!
不是那个
This! Us!
我是说这个，我们！
Oh,my God,Ross,it's.... You're just....
天啊，罗斯，你…你只是你…
Since you've been here, you're driving me....
从你到这儿开始 我都快要被你逼疯了…
Mon,you've gone ultrasonic again,all right?
摩妮卡，你又开始高八度了
I just can't stand you being here...
我受不了…
...all the time!
…你老是在这里！
Why? Why can't you stand me being here?
为什么？ 你为什么受不了呢？
We're just having fun.
我们只是在闹着玩而已
Fun? You think this is fun?
玩？这叫好玩吗？
I thought we were fooling around, like when we were kids.
少来了，我以为我们只是在闹 就像我们小时候一样
I hated you when we were kids!
罗斯，小时候我恨你耶
You hated me when we were kids?
小时候你恨我？
I hated you.
对，我恨你
I loved you in a you're-my-brother- so-l-have-to way...
我是说，我就像“你是我哥 所以我必须爱你”那样爱你…
... but basically,I hated your guts.
…但基本上…我恨死你了
Why did you hate me?
你为什么要恨我？
Because you were mean to me...
因为你对我太烂了…
...and you teased me and you always got your way.
而且…你…你嘲弄我 你总是…你总是得逞
That wasn't fun for you?
你觉得那不好玩？
I can't believe you hated me.
真不敢相信你恨我
But now I love you.
现在我爱你
And not just because I have to.
不只是因为我必须这样
Really?
真的？
You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.
只是你现在必须停止惹怒我
I can do that.
我可以办得到
Then I won't have to kill you.
那我就用不着杀你了
So you wanna watch Entertainment Tonight?.
你要看“今天娱乐”？
Thanks.
谢了
You know what?
知道吗？
If you really wanna watch that Serengeti thing,we can.
如果你真的想看那个节目 我还是可以让你
Listen,you are not going to believe this...
听着，你们绝对不会相信的…
...but that is not me singing on the video.
…但是MTV上的歌声 不是我的
How did you find out?
你怎么知道的呢？
The record company sent this paper for me to sign saying it's okay...
唱片公司送了一张纸条来 叫我签名，要我同意…
...for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.
…他们找别人来替我唱的 那是我的第一个线索
What will you do?
那你打算怎么办？
I can't work with people who would do this.
我没有办法跟这种人一起工作
Sure.
那当然
I mean,this poor woman.
这个…这个可怜的女人
What woman?
什么女人？
The voice woman.
那个代唱的女人
She has a great voice, but she doesn't have a video.
她的声音真是棒透了 可是她没有MTV啊
Okay,Pheebs,but what about you?
菲菲，那你呢？
I have a video. Pay attention.
我有MTV，你得要留心听
This voice woman,she's so talented.
这个代唱的人她很有才华
But according to the producer people, she doesn't have the right look.
可是那些制作人说 她长得不够好看之类的啦
She's like one of those animals at the pound...
她就像那种 动物收容所里面的动物…
...who nobody wants because they're not pretty.
…没有人要就因为 她长得不够漂亮而已
Or you know,like some old dog who's kind of like stinky and
或者是像只老狗，浑身发臭…
Oh,my God! She's "smelly cat"!
我的天啊，它就是“臭臭猫”
That song has so many levels.
那首歌具有深度
Hey,Eddie.
艾迪
You wanna play some foosball?
来玩桌上足球怎么样？
No,thanks,man. I'm not really into sports.
不，谢了，老兄 我不太喜欢运动
Yeah,okay. All right.
好吧…
Doesn't matter. Time for Baywatch!
没关系 “霹雳游龙”要开演了
You like that show?
你喜欢看那个节目？
You don't?
你不喜欢吗？
It's just pretty people running around on the beach.
不，那只是一群俊男美女 在海滩上跑来跑去
That's the brilliance of it.
棒就棒在那里啊
The pretty people.
俊男美女
And the running.
跑来跑去
I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.
我要进我房间看书了
Okay,man.
好的，老兄
I think of all the friends I've known
我想到和我相知相惜的友人
But when I dial the telephone
但我拨电话时
No one's home
没有人在家
All by myself
孤孤单单
Don't wanna live
我不想要一个人
All by myself
孤孤单单
Anymore
不想再孤单
All by myself
孤孤单单
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
What are they feeding you? Everybody!
他们喂你什么？ 一起唱
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
It's not your fault
那不是你的错
They won't take you to the vet
他们不带你去看兽医
You're obviously not their favorite pet
你显然不是他们的最爱
You may not be a bed of roses
你或许不是一床玫瑰
And you're no friend To those with noses
也没有人会喜欢闻你
Ross,those are the only lines we have. Back to the chorus!
罗斯，歌词都唱完了，抱歉 好了，回到合唱的部分